# LINKS

#### Portfolio:

https://ckapsalis2710.github.io/ portfolio/

#### LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/c hristos-kapsalis-lin/

https://github.com/ckapsalis27

<u>10</u>

### **ABOUT ME**

#### **Full-stack software**

HTML. Back-end

developer for almost 10 years in numerous software projects. Front-end development in Javascript, React, CSS, Bootstrap and

development in Java, Lua and PHP. Eager to learn new languages, technologies and undertake interesting projects. Accountable, working on schedule and

comfortable working as a

team member.

### **SKILLS**

JAVASCRIPT/ REACT/ JQUERY/ HTML/ CSS/ BOOTSTRAP

JAVA/ LUA/ PHP/ C/ SQL/ **BASH SCRIPTING** 

NODEJS/ EXPRESSJS

**KUBERNETES/DOCKERS** 

XML/JSON/AJAX/SVI

GIT/SVN

ROBOT/JENKINS

**REGULAR EXPRESSIONS** 

VS CODE/ ECLIPSE (+SPRING FRAMEWORK)/ PHPSTORM/ **CODECHARGE STUDIO** 

SQL CLIENTS (PGADMIN4, DBEAVER, DB VISUALIZER. **DB BROWSER FOR** SOLITE. NAVICAT)

**DEVELOPER TOOLS/** POSTMAN/ WIRESHARK

**BALSAMIC (MOCK-UPS)** 

BROWSERS' WEB

AGILE

CMS

WINDOWS & LINUX OS

# LANGUAGES

GREEK

**ENGLISH** 

ITALIAN

# HOBBIES

HIKING/CLIMBING/SKI-SNOWBOARD/ TAEKWONDO/ **SWIMMING** 

# **CHRISTOS** KAPSALIS



+306947934771

xrikapsalis@gmail.com

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Nov 2022 - Present

**Sabbatical - Freelance Climbing Instructor** 

### **NOKIA**

Athens Dec 2021 - Oct 2022

# **Senior Technical Specialist**

- Back-end development of Altiplano Controller, an open software GUI platform that served as an API to connect other Nokia's software units.
- Software development of a feature in Java, tested on JUnit, loaded on a Docker container, deployed on Kubernetes platform. Most of the work applied to arrange PODs configuration and their software interaction, under Kubernetes.
- Experience in Intent development logic, Microservices, Cloud based solutions, DevOps operations, Kibana search engine, Postman request engine.

#### NOKIA

Athens Sep 2016 - Dec 2021

# **Software Engineer**

- Full-stack development of WebCT, a software that provided a GUI to administer X-Haul microwave products.
- · Back-end development of WebCT in **Lua** and DB handling with Lua-Sqlite3. As well, development in Java with JUnit testing of ASLM, an app that produces licenses for all X-Haul products.
- · Front-end development in Javascript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS, and Bootstrap framework.
- · Involved with the full circle of a feature's production. Creation and reviewing of features' code, software architectural designs, Low Level Design, mock-ups, CuDo documents. Developing at least one feature per release while following a biannual release schedule.
- · Peer reviewing of Code, Use Cases, Test Strategy and Test Cases.
- · Full stack Unit Testing and debugging code.

#### NOKIA

Athens Jun 2015 - Aug 2016

# **Software Engineer**

- Full-stack software development of the FMANG application, managing Nokia's FlexiNG product. An app that offered mainly a GUI to monitor all kind of alarms, statistics and product's health, like also managing all kind of product's configuration.
- · Back-end development in Java and Java EE Development toolset: JSF/Primefaces, Spring, Hibernate, Maven, Tomcat, Jenkins, Junit.
- · Front-end development in Javascript, HTML, CSS.
- · Change the whole product's GUI style after company's rebranding. Create some new features, debugging and peer reviewing of code. Milestone, to solve with the help of the team a crucial bug that maid the whole app to fail.

# **NOKIA**

Athens Oct 2014 - May 2015

# **E&V Tester**

- · Responsible for CI Test suite of Nokia's LTE network gateway (FlexiNG) of around 400 Test Cases.
- Entity and Verification testing in **Robot** framework. Daily report on the CI state and fixing each TC that failed.
- · Enhancing the CI by creating some new TCs.

#### INTERACTIVE **COMMUNICATION** LTD Athens

**CYBERTECHNICS** 

Dec 2012 - Jan 2014

# Web Programmer/Developer

- Full-stack software development of Modus CMS.
- Back-end development in PHP and DB handling with MySQL. Front-end development in Javascript, HTML, CSS.
- · Responsible for Back-end administration and development of Modus CMS.
- Updating and debugging CMS' code. Creating CMS' modules, components, droplets. Data handling through DB queries of production's applications, upon customers requests.
- Implementation of RAFM (Restricted Access File Manager) filesystem and integration of Ajaxplorer GUI into Modus CMS.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **UNIVERSITY OF PIRAEUS** Piraeus

2011

**University Degree in Digital Systems & Technology Education: Informatics** 

#### **STOCKHOLM UNIVERSITY AND KTH JOINT DEPARTMENT**

Stockholm

**Erasmus Exchange Student Program: Knowledge** Management

# 2009

# **COURSE**

**ZERO TO MASTERY ACADEMY** Sep 2024 - Present

Fullstack Web Developer Career Path. Updating my knowledge on CSS, latest versions of Javascript, learning REACT, NodeJS with ExpressJS, PostgreSQL by building a full-stack app and using a Machine Learning API.